{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application. +3",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Express",
      "description": "Backend concepts and more.",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "Test Try #426",
      "description": "Testing seems to be going ok. ",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route> \n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "id": 4,
      "deckId": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfsdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "asdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "blahblah",
      "back": "blah",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "dfh",
      "back": "cfh",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Card #718",
      "back": "I decided to delete the other cards out of fear. ",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Card #719",
      "back": "This is a record of the events of 11/55/21. The following is all I have left after the attack.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Card #720",
      "back": "After Tinkering with what I thought would be mundane front end coding at the end of the night, I saw a faint glowing dot on the screen.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Card #721",
      "back": "At first it was a soft glow, But after a minute it started to pulsate with a regular vibrancy equated to pulsars in distant galaxies.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Card #722",
      "back": "As I moused over the dot it would make another dot appear.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Card #723",
      "back": "Soon there were dots all over my screen. The pulsing for each dot was in unison. ",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 28
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Card #724",
      "back": "I felt a strange feeling come over me as I started to hear voices chanting in strange tongues.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Card #735",
      "back": "They........it........., I can't believe it.",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "front": "Test Caaard Fourrrr Hunndreww Tweenty SSSSSSSixxxxxxx......",
      "back": "ENTITY: You are to report to the ::HiveCluster:: . . . . Failure will result in dematerialization. . . . . . . . .  ",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 31
    }
  ]
}